Guide to the Vern Haugland Papers 1908-1987
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Memorabilia, 1942-1978 and undated; Series VIII; 2 linear feet
  - Medal of Honor for outstanding bravery in New Guinea, Associated Press, 1942 (Box 21)
  - Military Hat during WWII, 1942-1945 (Box 21)
  - Military Medals and Patches (Box 21)
  - Name Plate, undated (Box 21)
  - Paper Weight: Civil Air Patrol, Auxiliary United States Airforce, undated (Box 21)
  - Paper Weight: Relay I, The Pacesetter in Communications Satellites, undated (Box 21)
  - Paper Weight: Sample of 1.02 inch 2024-T351 Aluminum Alloy from a Boeing B-53 Starofort, undated (Box 21)
  - Paper Weight: Space Systems Center Dedication, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Paper Weight: United Airlines 100,000 mile club, undated (Box 21)
  - Plaque: Apollo 15, USS Okinawa, undated (Box 21)
  - Plaque: Associated Press, Honored Byline in Journalism Retirement Award, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Plaque: Associated Press, Strebig-Dobben Memorial Award, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Plaque: Fifth Anniversary of Communications Satellite Corporation, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Plaque: Wing Remnant of New Orleans, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Tie Tacks, undated (Box 21)
  - Toy Planes (3) (Box 21)
  - Airline Bag: Welcome Aboard Air Force One, undated (Box 22)
  - Book Ends: General Electric Development facilities for Flight Propulsion Progress, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Clay Pot: Commemorating Apollo 11, undated (Box 22)
  - Placemat: Apollo Lunar Landing Sites, undated (Box 22)
  - Plaque: Commemoration the first flight of Wright Brothers, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Sound Recordings: "Voices from the Moon," Apollo 11, undated (Box 22)
  - Sound Recordings: "Sounds of Saturn", undated (Box 22)
  - Airplane Propeller: Signed by Haugland's friends from aviation, 1973 (Box OS 6)
- Photographs, 1936-1983 and undated; Series X
  This series consists of photographs of Haugland and his career, and of photographs he collected in the course of his work. The latter mostly relate to the military and aviation.
  - V. Haugland facing unidentified man, undated; 153(X)1 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with four unidentified men in front of a computer, undated; 153(X)2 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland sitting in small plane with unidentified men, undated; 153(X)3 (Box 23)
  - Four unidentified me inside small plane, undated; 153(X)4 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland 2 nd left, with four unidentified men in front of machines, undated; 153(X)5 (Box 23)
  - Ten unidentified men in front of a bus, undated; 153(X)6 (Box 23)
  - Driver in bus with sign "OnTrac II Flight Demonstrations", undated; 153(X)7 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland standing in office with unidentified men, undated; 153(X)8 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in front of plane with twelve unidentified men, 153(X)9 (Box 23)
  - Unidentified man at plane control panel, undated; 153(X)10 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, 2 nd left with three unidentified men, undated; 153(X)11 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland looking at pictures at AWA breakfast, May 13, undated; 153(X)12 (Box 23)
  - Arthur C. Stroz, V. Haugland, Maj. Gen. H. Griswold, and Gen. Curtis E. LeMay, undated; 153(X)13 (Box 23)
  - Arthur C.Storz, V. Haugland, Maj. Gen Francis H. Griswold, undated; 153(X)14 (Box 23)
  - Guests at Frontier Room, Storz Brewing Co., undated; 153(X)15 (Box 23)
  - James H. Strubel, Brig. Gen Arno Luechman, Arthur C. Storz, undated; 153(X)16 (Box 23)
  - Guests in the Grontier Room, Storz Brewing Co., undated; 153(X)17 (Box 23)
  - Guests in the Trophy Room, undated; 153(X)18 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified men in front of bus and buildings, undated; 153(X)19 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with nine unidentified men, undated; 153(X)20 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland and unidentified men out of focus in background, undated; 153(X)21 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with three unidentified men and one unidentified woman, undated; 153(X)22 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland talking with unidentified man, undated; 153(X)23 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man, undated; 153(X)24 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with military official using radio, undated; 153(X)25 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in front of World's First Atomic Jet Engine, undated; 153(X)26 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland and unidentified woman by picnic table, undated; 153(X)27 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in large group picture, undated; 153(X)28 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at typewriter, undated; 153(X)29 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at typewriter, undated; 153(X)30 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified men, undated; 153(X)31 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man who is holding a gun, undated; 153(X)32 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with seven individuals at press conference, undated; 153(X)33 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland and unidentified man, both seated in chairs, undated; 153(X)34 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland shaking hands with and accepting award from unidentified man, undated; 153(X)35 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man in front of "Power for United PC-8 Jet Mainliner" exhibit, undated; 153(X)36 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified men in front of an airplane, undated; 153(X)37 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland sitting at table with twelve unidentified men, undated; 153(X)38 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with three unidentified men and one military personnel inside a ship, undated; 153(X)39 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with ten unidentified men in two rows posing for picture, undated; 153(X)40 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified woman and man, behind missile, undated; 153(X)41 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified woman and man, holding model planes, undated; 153(X)42 (Box 23)
  - V. Huagland with unidentified woman and man holding model planes, undated; 153(X)43 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland standing with two unidentified men, undated; 153(X)44 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified men, both holding glasses - business card with photo, undated; 153(X)45 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at dinner table with nine unidentified men, undated; 153(X)46 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland speaking at podium, undated; 153(X)47 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in front of typewriter with unidentified men, undated; 153(X)48 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at table with two unidentified men, undated; 153(X)49 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland on phone, at table with two unidentified men, undated; 153(X)50 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at typewriter, undated; 153(X)51 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland sitting at control panels, undated; 153(X)52 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at control panels, undated; 153(X)53 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, military photo, undated; 153(X)54 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, face shot; just before WWII, undated; 153(X)55 (Box 23)
  - Tessie as a gypsy, age 13, undated; 153(X)56 (Box 23)
  - Tessom McMahon as Chinese dancer, age 13, undated; 153(X)57 (Box 23)
  - Jean-Francis Roulet, Andre Glareser, Andre Bannwast, Jean Pierre Kreis, Jean-Pierre Qreuacher, Francis Schumacker, Giles Cuanitter, Pierre Humbel, undated; 153(X)58 (Box 23)
  - Eight young boys with older man and woman, undated; 153(X)59 (Box 23)
  - Small portrait of unidentified young woman, undated; 153(X)60 (Box 23)
  - Two unidentified young girls, three torn edges, undated; 153(X)61 (Box 23)
  - Unidentified woman in front, at the New York World's Fair, undated; 153(X)62 (Box 23)
  - Woman and young child sitting on ledge in front of water, undated; 153(X)63 (Box 23)
  - Young girl holding doll, undated; 153(X)64 (Box 23)
  - Two young boys and one girl standing in doorway, undated; 153(X)65 (Box 23)
  - Man standing, woman sitting with young child, undated; 153(X)66 (Box 23)
  - Woman looking up; woman sitting with child; two exposures, undated; 153(X)67 (Box 23)
  - Three unidentified women, taken in Butte, 1940; 153(X)68 (Box 23)
  - "Mom", Seattle, Aug. 29, 1945; 153(X)69 (Box 23)
  - "Mom Dear" Butte, undated; 153(X)70 (Box 23)
  - Rhoda, Tess, Maggie, Butte, 1936; 153(X)71 (Box 23)
  - Unidentified woman posing in a dress, undated; 153(X)72 (Box 23)
  - Deanna Lynn Haugland, class of 1958, 153(X)73 (Box 23)
  - Portrait of young unidentified girl, undated; 153(X)74 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with an unidentified woman, Hollywood, 1937; 153(X)75 (Box 23)
  - Portrait of Billie Burke, undated; 153(X)76 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with Olson and Johnson, undated; 153(X)77 (Box 23)
  - Jacie and Jon with cat and dog, undated; 153(X)78 (Box 23)
  - One woman with four girls in front of trees, undated; 153(X)79 (Box 23)
  - Michael, Nancy, Mary Grace û Elise, double exposure; Christmas, 1983; 153(X)80 (Box 23)
  - Ktat and V. Haugland in Java, 1946; 153(X)81 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in Venezuela, April 1955; 153(X)82 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, May 1962; 153(X)83 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in crowd, May/June, 1962; 153(X)84 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, undated; 153(X)85 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, undated; 153(X)86 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland at typewriter, undated; 153(X)87 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, undated; 153(X)88 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, undated; 153(X)89 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, undated; 153(X)90 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, passport, 1973; 153(X)91 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, driver's license, 1976; 153(X)92 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, 1982; 153(X)93 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in uniform, undated; 153(X)94 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland, undated; 153(X)95 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in uniform, undated; 153(X)96 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in bed receiving Silver Star from Gen. MacArthur, unidentified men in background, Oct 1, 1942; 153(X)97 (Box 23)
  - Gen. Casey, Col. Matthews and two doctors outside V. Haugland's tent, undated; 153(X)98 (Box 23)
  - Vehicle on palm tree lined road, undated; 153(X)99 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with four unidentified men; WWII 1943, South Pacific, 153(X)100 (Box 23)
  - Military camp on Beach, undated; 153(X)101 (Box 23)
  - Military Camp in the palm trees, undated; 153(X)102 (Box 23)
  - Military camp in disorder, undated; 153(X)103 (Box 23)
  - Military camp, unidentified men in distance, undated; 153(X)104 (Box 23)
  - Military camp, undated; 153(X)105 (Box 23)
  - Clouds and palm trees, undated; 153(X)106 (Box 23)
  - Arial photo of the shore, undated; 153(X)107 (Box 23)
  - Men lined up holding books, one standing in front, undated; 153(X)108 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified men, one in truck, on leaning on truck, undated; 153(X)109 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with four unidentified military personnel, undated; 153(X)110 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland in front row, Signal Corps, U.S. Army, undated; 153(X)111 (Box 23)
  - Burning vessel letting off smoke on water, off shore, undated; 153(X)112 (Box 23)
  - Men standing in front of smoking plane, undated; 153(X)113 (Box 23)
  - Vessel smoking on water, undated; 153(X)114 (Box 23)
  - Submarine emerging, undated; 153(X)115 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland shoveling dirt, South Pacific, 1943; 153(X)116 (Box 23)
  - Military Camp, undated; 153(X)117 (Box 23)
  - Soldiers unloading supplies into truck, undated; 153(X)118 (Box 23)
  - Smoking vessel off shore, military vehicles on road, undated; 153(X)119 (Box 23)
  - Smoking airplane on beach, undated; 153(X)120 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with three unidentified military personnel, undated; 153(X)121 (Box 23)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man, both in uniform, undated; 153(X)122 (Box 24)
  - Stan Troutman, V. Haugland, Clark Lee, Maj. Gen Donald Wilson, Jim McGlincy, Bill downs at Orlando Army Air Base, undated; 153(X)123 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with four unidentified men and one woman holding a cat, undated; 153(X)124 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with four men in uniform, undated; 153(X)125 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in uniform, undated; 153(X)126 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Les Nichols, Dill Ferris, Lt. Jim Vandriveer, Ed Franke, Justin Gray, Lt. Oscar Hume, Ed Thronap, U.S.S. Missouri, Feb., 1945; 153(X)127 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified man, U.S.S. Missouri, Feb., 1945; 153(X)128 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland talking with unidentified military personnel, undated; 153(X)129 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in uniform, San Francisco, Aug. 1945; 153(X)130 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in uniform, San Francisco, Aug. 1945; 153(X)131 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in uniform with an unidentified man, 1942; 153(X)132 (Box 24)
  - K' Tut TanTri, in middle, undated; 153(X)133 (Box 24)
  - Four unidentified girls, South Pacific, undated; 153(X)134 (Box 24)
  - Chaplin Maj. Matthew H. Imrie leading congregation at island of Kiriwana, June 1943; 153(X)135 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified man at Bataura, undated; 153(X)136 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Maj. Albert E. Dawson, Lt. Col. James M. Smith, Lt. Col. Donald H. Frank, after record flight to England and return, MacDill AFB, Aug. 15, 1953; 153(X)137 (Box 24)
  - Press conference with Ben. Bruether at Brussels, Oct 1953; 153(X)138 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified man sitting at desk, undated; 153(X)139 (Box 24)
  - Lt. Col. James M. Smith, Lt. Col. Donald Franks, Maj. Dawson, MacDill AFB, July 26, 1953; 153(X)140 (Box 24)
  - B-47 Brew after record flight to England, MacDill AFB, July 26, 1953; 153(X)141 (Box 24)
  - Lt. Col. Bob Michie, Major, Bill Richards, Col. Vandevanter, Wes Price, July 26, 1953; 153(X)142 (Box 24)
  - Gen. Dawson, Lt. Col. Smith, Lt. Col. Frank, V. Haugland, MacDill AFB, July 26, 1953; 153(X)143 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified pilot in front of the nose of a plane, undated; 153(X)144 (Box 24)
  - Two unidentified military personnel looking at clipboard under plane's wing, undated; 153(X)145 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland talking with unidentified military personnel, undated; 153(X)146 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland standing on step ladder talking with man on ground; April, 1952; 153(X)147 (Box 24)
  - Major James Jabara talking with V. Haugland and unidentified man about F-89D, Yuma, AZ AFB, undated; 153(X)148 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in Cockpit with 1st Lt. Paul J. Frtizinger, undated; 153(X)149 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Maj. Sidney M. Chester, in front of radar controller, Yuma, AZ AFB, undated; 153(X)150 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Maj. James Jabara, in front of F-89D 'Scorpion', Yuma, AZ AFB, undated; 153(X)151 (Box 24)
  - Navy soldiers lined up on Aircraft carrier, undated; 153(X)152 (Box 24)
  - Docked Aircraft Carrier, undated; 153(X)153 (Box 24)
  - Three tugboats pulling aircraft carrier, undated; 153(X)154 (Box 24)
  - Side of docked ship, undated; 153(X)155 (Box 24)
  - GT-3 Intrepid, aircraft carrier moving through ocean, undated; 153(X)156 (Box 24)
  - U.S.S. New Orleans at sea, undated; 153(X)157 (Box 24)
  - U.S.S. Wasp at sea, undated; 153(X)158 (Box 24)
  - Lt. Fred W. Smith in uniform with biographical info, undated; 153(X)159 (Box 24)
  - Rear Admiral Donald M. White, undated; 153(X)160 (Box 24)
  - Captain J.G. Smith in uniform, undated; 153(X)161 (Box 24)
  - Commander J.F. Gillooly in uniform, undated; 153(X)162 (Box 24)
  - Missile being launched, undated; 153(X)163 (Box 24)
  - Side shot of TR-120 plane with two pilots in opened cockpit, undated; 153(X)164 (Box 24)
  - Two pilots nest to plane, one wearing helmet and mask, undated; 153(X)165 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified pilot flying 'zero', Nov. 1978; 153(X)166 (Box 24)
  - B-47 leaving MacDill AFB; July 26, 1953; 153(X)167 (Box 24)
  - "Stoof" - S2F, 153(X)168 (Box 24)
  - Helicopter landing on U.S.S. Wasp, undated; 153(X)169 (Box 24)
  - Intrepid, just off aircraft carrier, undated; 153(X)170 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified plane in air, undated; 153(X)171 (Box 24)
  - Intrepid - EA1E Skyraider, undated; 153(X)172 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in cockpit, undated; 153(X)173 (Box 24)
  - TV-3 rocket before launch at Patrick AFB, FL, undated; 153(X)174 (Box 24)
  - Press conference for missile, undated; 153(X)175 (Box 24)
  - "Junior" rocket with info sheet, undated; 153(X)176 (Box 24)
  - Launch Rocket in air, undated; 153(X)177 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified plane in air, undated; 153(X)178 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified plane on the ground, undated; 153(X)179 (Box 24)
  - Instruction Pilot monitoring mock mission from, undated; 153(X)180 (Box 24)
  - Instruction Pilot monitoring from ground, undated; 153(X)181 (Box 24)
  - Picture from training monitor system, undated; 153(X)182 (Box 24)
  - Instructor Pilot monitoring training, undated; 153(X)183 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified plane in air, undated; 153(X)184 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified plane on the ground, undated; 153(X)185 (Box 24)
  - Row of six planes on the ground, pair of men working on first two, undated; 153(X)186 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified plane in flight, undated; 153(X)187 (Box 24)
  - U.S. Navy F-14A Tomcat, with information and specs on back, undated; 153(X)188 (Box 24)
  - U.S. Navy F-14A Tomcat, info and specs on back, undated; 153(X)189 (Box 24)
  - U.S. Navy F-14A Tomcat, info and specs on back, undated; 153(X)190 (Box 24)
  - B-1 Strategic Bomber, info and specs on back, undated; 153(X)191 (Box 24)
  - Two unidentified persons, Col. Dean Davenport, V. Haugland, Tyndall AFB, Jan. 1957; 153(X)192 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Gen. Joseph Atkinson, Tyndall AFB, Jan 1957; 153(X)193 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Gen. Joseph Atkinson, Tyndall ABF, Jan 1957; 153(X)194 (Box 24)
  - Covair F-106 B Delta Dart, Tyndall AFB, Oct 24, 1958; 153(X)195 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, speaking to two unidentified military personnel; Tyndall AFB, 1958; 153(X)196 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with unidentified military personnel in front of plane, Tyndall AFB, 1958; 153(X)197 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with two unidentified military personnel; Tyndall AFB, 1958; 153(X)198 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland underplane with two unidentified military personnel, Tyndall AFT, 1958; 153(X)199 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland taking notes and speaking with unidentified military personnel under plane, Tyndal AFB, 1958; 153(X)200 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland and unidentified military personnel under plane looking inside, Tyndall, 1958; 153(X)201 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified military personnel, Tyndall AFB, 1958; 153(X)202 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland wearing pilot's helmet with two unidentified military personnel, Tyndall AFB, 1958; 153(X)203 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, with two unidentified military personnel, wearing pilot's helmet, Tyndall, 1958; 153(X)204 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland at Patrick AFB, FL, March 5, 1956; 153(X)205 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland putting on pilot's vest with assistance, Tyndal AFB, 1958; 153(X)206 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified military personnel, wearing pilot's vest and pack, Tyndall AFB, 1958; 153(X)207 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with typewriter, unidentified man bent at waist with cigarette, April 1957; 153(X)208 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified people at Boulder Dam, Nov. 18, 1950; 153(X)209 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified group, NAS Pensecola, FL, Nov. 21, 1955; 153(X)210 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with twelve men in striped shirts and cowboy hats, Jan. 17, 1953; 153(X)211 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified military personnel, Feb. 5, 1953; 153(X)212 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified military personnel, Feb. 5, 1953; 153(X)213 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with large unidentified group of men, undated; 153(X)214 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified men, comparing notes, July 1954; 153(X)215 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in cockpit, El Centro California, April 2, 1957; 153(X)216 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in pilot's uniform stepping onto plane, El Centro California, April 2, 1957; 153(X)217 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland at buffet table, inaugural luncheon, Feb. 1, 1956; 153(X)218 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland on telephone in front of typewriter, Andrews AFB, July 28, 1957; 153(X)219 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in front of typewriter, unidentified man, July 28, 1957; 153(X)220 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with eight unidentified people in front of plane, Oct 1958; 153(X)221 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland looking through window of plane, unidentified man inside, Aug. 1959; 153(X)222 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with unidentified man, both wearing "aviation writers" pins, 1959; 153(X)223 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with two unidentified men, AWA annual meeting, 1959; 153(X)224 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with unidentified men AWA annual meeting, 1959; 153(X)225 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland sitting at banquet table with pen in hand, 1959; 153(X)226 (Box 24)
  - B-47B Press Flight Dinner Guests, May 29, 1952; 153(X)227 (Box 24)
  - Three unidentified men in suits and hats, June 20, 1950; 153(X)228 (Box 24)
  - Large group of travelers in front of TWA plane holding baguettes, Paris, Oct, 1953; 153(X)229 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with three unidentified women, Pillsbury Trip, Paris, Oct 1953; 153(X)230 (Box 24)
  - Tour of Curtiss-Wright corporation, Dec. 17, 1953; 153(X)231 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with other guests at party, May 7, 1954; 153(X)232 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland aboard U.S.S Monterey in Gulf of Mexico, Pensacola, FL, Feb. 24, 1954; 153(X)233 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with three unidentified men looking at plane, July 1, 1954; 153(X)234 (Box 24)
  - Group posing in front of plane for Medina Orientation Cruise, Pensacola, FL, Feb. 23, 1954; 153(X)235 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with group in front of 483 rd Troop Carrier Station, Southern Japan, 1955; 153(X)236 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Gen. Nathan F. Twining, two unidentified men, Airpower Banquet, Aug. 13, 1955; 153(X)237 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified men looking at a large piece of metal, Indianapolis, Jan. 1955; 153(X)238 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with three unidentified men in front of Christmas tree, Indianapolis, Jan. 1955; 153(X)239 (Box 24)
  - Group of men and women, some in costume, in front of plane, Nov. 29, 1956; 153(X)240 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland at concert, Madrid, Sept. 11, 1957; 153(X)241 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with unidentified man and woman, Gen. Beau's Party, Aug. 1956; 153(X)242 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland speaking with unidentified couple, Gen. Beau's party, Aug. 1956; 153(X)243 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified group, James Connally AFB, Waco, TX, Nov. 28, 1956; 153(X)244 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland and others loading bus, Fort Wroth Trip, July 1957; 153(X)245 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with four unidentified people, Hagerstown, MD, Nov. 11, 1957; 153(X)246 (Box 24)
  - Unidentified men on plane, AWA Convention, St. Louis-Kansas, July 12, 1957; 153(X)247 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Rallo, ND, Jan. 1957; 153(X)248 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified men by plane, Rallo, ND, Jan. 1957; 153(X)249 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified group. Ft. Belvoir, March 25, 1957; 153(X)250 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man and stewardess, Press Flight, March 25, 1957; 153(X)251 (Box 24)
  - 707 Press Flight, March 25, 1957; 153(X)252 (Box 24)
  - 707 Press Flight, March 25, 1957; 153(X)253 (Box 24)
  - 707 Press Flight, March 25, 1957; 153(X)254 (Box 24)
  - 707 Press Flight, March 25, 1957; 153(X)255 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland in front of boarding plane, Jan. 26, 1954; 153(X)256 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland outside Aerojet- General Coporation breakfast, Washington Hotel, May 13, 1959; 153(X)257 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified men, U.S.S. Valley Forge, Jan. 21, 1960; 153(X)258 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland sitting at a long table with many other men, AFA Convention, San Francisco, Nov. 1960; 153(X)259 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland, Reade Tilley, John Walker by first turbojet engine, Aug. 1960; 153(X)260 (Box 24)
  - Federation of Aeronatique International Meeting, Oct. 1960; 153(X)261 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland interviewing unidentified young man, taking notes, Sept. 7, 1961; 153(X)262 (Box 24)
  - V. Haugland standing behind formally set table with unidentified people around it, March 22 1961; 153(X)263 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland receiving an award from two unidentified AP representatives, March 1964; 153(X)264 (Box 25)
  - Kelly Johnson receiving Caller Trophy Award from President Johnson, Sept 1964; 153(X)265 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified man assisting V. Haugland with tie, Aug. 1964; 153(X)266 (Box 25)